ln closing, l can tell you
we take this very seriously.
APD as well as the DEA.
Stopping the manufacture
and sale of methamphetamines
remains one of
our highest priorities.
And the theft of lab equipment
from your school is also
receiving our highest attention.
Rest assured,
no stone will go unturned
in our search for the person
or persons responsible for this.
lf you have any questions,
now would be the time. Sir.
MAN 1 :
You're talking like you
haven't caught anybody yet.
What about the janitor
that was dealing drugs
at the school?
There is no indication
that this individual was
selling drugs.
He was arrested for having
a small amount of marijuana
in his car,
not in the school.
And he's since
been fired.
MAN 1 :
l heard he had a record.
l'd like to know how he got
a job here in the first place.
Exactly. Why wasn't there
a background check?
CARMEN:
There was one. We're currently
reviewing our hiring policies.
WOMAN 1 : You better be
doing more than that.
This guy was arrested
right in front of my daughter.
MAN 1 :
This guy was stealing
lab equipment, right?
MAN 2:
That's not our thinking this time.
We're looking at others who
also had access, but not limited
to the maintenance staff.
WOMAN 2:
Are you saying
there was a break-in?
Do we know exactly
when this happened?
l mean, could it have been
during school hours?
We haven't been able to
establish a date or time.
But there is no sign
of breaking or entering.
MAN 1 :
So whoever took it had a key.
We're talking inside job?
Someone who's still at the school?
MAN 2: Sir, at this time
l'm not able to discuss
the details with you.
But what l can tell you is that we
have some very good people
working very hard on this case.
MAN 1 : l'm sorry, officer,
but that just sounds like
double talk.
WOMAN 2: We're trying
to protect our children.
You have to level with us.
CARMEN:
Really, we're giving you
all the information we have.
MAN 1 : You know what l'd
like to see in this school?
Drug-sniffing dogs.
WOMAN 2:
Yeah. Dogs and metal detectors and
locker searches and strip-searches.
CARMEN:
Our district has strict policies--
WOMAN 3: l heard about
this school up in Canada,
they arrested one of the
groundskeepers with drugs,
and the next day they
found out over half of the
students were high on LSD.
WOMAN 2:
LSD? When were you
gonna tell us about the LSD?
CARMEN:
No, please. No one said
anything about LSD.
[♪♪♪]
MAN 1 :
What about the
equipment that was stolen?
CARMEN:
The equipment was taken from
our chemistry-department locker.
And tonight we're lucky
enough to have someone here
to give us some specifics.
Walt?
Yeah.
Mr. White is currently
on medical leave.
But as he's chair
of the science department,
he's made a very special
effort to be with us here.
And l'd like to take a moment
to thank him for that.
Could you please tell us
more about the equipment
that was taken?
Please.
WALT: Yes.
Sorry.
And thank you.
[CLEARS THROAT]
The inventory list for the
missing lab-wear is as follows:
One 5000 milliliter
round-bottom boiling flask.
One Kjeldahl-style recovery flask,
800 milliliters.
Two full-face respirators.
Some CEP funnels, some head
with a thermometer holder.
[MOANlNG]
Ooh. Ow. Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Oh, wow.
Where did that come from?
And why was it so damn good?
Because it was illegal.
[♪♪♪]
[DOOR OPENS]
The basement.
Unfinished, of course.
But just look
at all this space.
You gotta think rec room,
media room.
Just imagine all the things
you could do down here.
Now remember,
you're buying for this
fantastic neighborhood.
Big lawns
and shade trees,
walking distance to
the country club.
What happened there?
Bit of a fixer, but this
house has great bones.
REALTOR:
Know what? We're zeroing in.
l've got another listing, brand-new,
right around the corner.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Hi.
lt's by appointment only.
Oh, well, l'm here
to see the owner.
Oh. He's in the, uh,
recreational vehicle.
[CAR ENGlNE STARTS]
JESSE:
Yo, it's appointment only.
How are you feeling?
About as good
as you look.
Jeez, you look like Lex Luthor.
Listen, l visited
you in the hospital,
but you were asleep.
Yeah, Skinny Pete said
you wanted Tuco's address.
Acting like you're
all out for blood.
But you are alive.
Obviously you wised up.
No, l did go see him.
Bullshit.
So, what, are you
selling your house?
l got two dudes that turned
into raspberry slushy
and flushed down my toilet.
l can't even take
a proper dump in there.
l mean, the whole damn house
has gotta be haunted by now.
You didn't actually go see Tuco.
Here.
That is 1 7,500.
Your half of the 35,000.
Plus, there's an extra 1 5 in there.
lt's all yours. You've earned it.
You got this money from Tuco?
Yeah.
So Tuco gave you this,
is what you're saying.
Well, we made a deal.
You made a deal?
That's right.
How--? Why would you make
a deal with that scumbag?
You see what he did
to me?
Because l think that we
can do business together.
We came to an understanding.
No way, man.
Okay? No understanding.
Take a look
at the money in your hand.
Now, just imagine
making that every week.
That's right. Two pounds a week,
35,000 a pound.
Without even talking to me
you told this insane ass-clown
dead-eyed killer that, uh--
That we would
give him 2 pounds a week.
We'll just scale up our operation,
we'll add a few more hours.
No, don't talk to me about hours.
What about pseudo, man?
How are we gonna get that?
You think the meth fairy's
just gonna bring it to us?
God, it takes me a week
to get this stuff.
l'm driving all the way
out to Las Cruces,
200 miles each way
to meet up with my smurfs.
Smurfs?
The dudes who go to the drugstores
and get a couple boxes at a time
and then sell them to me.
And that's maybe only good for,
like, maybe a half-pound worth.
See, that's the bottleneck
in your brilliant business plan.
All right.
Of course, you would've known
that if you would've just asked me.
DELCAVOLl:
Well, here we are again.
Here we are.
Skyler, you look great.
Thank you.
You must be, what,
six, seven months?
How goes it?
lt's great.
Um, other than waddling to
the bathroom every five minutes.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
The baby shower
is next week.
And it'll be good to. . .
lt'll be good to have a day
that's just about Skyler.
Very nice.
Thank you.
Well, Walt, l see you've
committed to the hair loss.
Mm. Yeah.
How do you feel?
Ah, okay.
l-- You know,
pretty decent, actually.
His color is better.
You know, his energy.
And he's even more, um, physical.
More physical?
Ah, well, sexual.
Um...
Frisky, actually.
l mean, that's gotta be
a good sign, right?
Sure, l'll take that. Right, Walt?
Right.
Couldn't that mean that
the chemo is working?
Well, realistically, it may
just mean that we've got
the antiemetics tuned right.
Truth is, until Walt's
finished this round of chemo
and we look at a new PET scan,
we just can't say
for sure.
SKYLER:
Well, isn't there anything else
we could be doing?
l've been wondering
about alternative medicine.
l mean, Eastern healing.
You know, holistic.
Well, l can't speak to its efficacy,
but as long as it doesn't
interfere with our treatment,
anything that helps my patient
have a better outlook,
a better comfort, is fine by me.
So you're saying
it's just all psychological.
lt doesn't make any
real difference.
Having a better outlook can
make a tremendous difference.
But it's also important that
we manage our expectations.
[♪♪♪]
What?
A junkyard? Let me guess,
you picked this place?
What's wrong with it?
lt's private.
This is like a non-criminal's
idea of a drug meet.
This is like, "Oh, l saw this
in a movie. Ooh, look at me."
Yes. So where do you
transact your business?
Enlighten me.
l don't know,
how about Taco Cabeza?
Half the deals l've ever done
went down at Taco Cabeza.
Nice and public.
Open 24 hours.
Nobody ever gets shot
at Taco Cabeza.
Hell, why not
the mall?
You know, wait at the Gap.
"Hey, it's time for the meet."
You know, l'll put down
the flat-front khakis,
head on over,
grab an Orange Julius.
Skip the part where
psycho-lunatic Tuco,
you know,
comes and steals my
drugs and leaves me
bleeding to death.
[HURRlCANE CHRlS'
"THE HAND CLAP"
PLAYlNG ON CAR STEREO]
Look, you don't have
to be here for this.
Okay? l mean,
seriously.
l'm okay.
No. l'm no pussy.
l'm good.
[MUSlC STOPS]
Mr. Clean and his boy.
[TUCO CHUCKLES]
Now, l'm sorry
that l had to tune you up.
Respect, ése,
you gotta give it to get it.
Ahh.
Hey, what are we doing
way the hell out here?
What, they close the mall
or something?
Heisenberg, come on,
break it out.
That's it? That's all you got?
We had some
production problems.
0.53.
l thought you was
a player.
You told me
2 pounds,
and now you waste my time
with these Chiclets?
Seventeen and a half.
Minus the half for
wasting my time.
WALT: Hey, come on.
What, you gonna argue?
You got something to say?
You're doing business
like a couple little bitches.
l want all of it.
Seventy grand.
What did you say?
WALT:
You like this product.
And you want more.
Consider it a capital investment.
Look, old, bald motherfucker.
Fifty-two and a half,
25 points vig.
Vig?
lnterest, weekly.
Okay.
That's $65,625
with interest.
1 .875 pounds.
TUCO: No, 2 pounds.
Next Friday,
and no production problems.
Can you handle 4 pounds?
Listen, old man, talk is talk.
But owing me money,
that's bad.
[ENGlNE STARTS]
[TRUCK DRlVES OFF]
What did you just do?
Four pounds. Four pounds.
Two pounds wasn't bad enough.
We're talking 2, 300 boxes
of sinus pills.
There ain't that many
smurfs in the world.
We're not going to need
pseudoephedrine.
We're gonna make phenylacetone
in a tube furnace.
Then we're gonna use
reductive amination to yield
methamphetamine, 4 pounds.
So no pseudo?
No pseudo.
So you do have a plan.
Yeah, Mr. White.
Yeah, science.
Okay.
What's this?
That is a shopping list.
Ah, getting some of those
items may be challenging.
One autotransformer,
Six liters anhydrous
methenamine.
Two 35 M and M tube furnaces.
lt's mm, millimeter.
One 70 millimeter would be fine,
but they're hard to come by, so...
Forty grams thorium nitrate.
Yo, Mr. White, l can't even
pronounce half this shit.
No. You know what?
Count me out. All right?
l'm leaving town.
l'm moving to, like,
Oregon or something.
This is just--
Jesse, Jesse, Jesse. Listen to me.
Today is the first day
of the rest of your life.
What are you doing?
This is the first day of the
rest of your life. But what
kind of life will it be, huh?
Will it be a life of fear,
of "Oh, no, no, no.
l can't do this."
Of never once
believing in yourself?
Hm?
l don't know.
Listen. These things?
We need them, all right?
And only you can
get them for us.
[SlGHS]
WALT JR. :
Okay, it's ready. Here you go.
Hi, baby.
I'm your Aunt Marie.
Now, of course you already
know that because when
you watch this,
20 years from now, l will look
exactly the same as l do now.
I know, it is amazing. l have
aged shockingly well. Haven't l?
Anyway, welcome to your
baby shower, Esmeralda.
WALT JR. :
Esmeralda?
Esmeralda. That's your name
and you heard it here first.
Now, that is your wonderful,
handsome older brother.
Show her, older brother,
your face.
Okay, not right up the nose. Don't--
Okay, not up it. Back. Back to me.
Here's your mommy.
Hello, Mom.
And look, there you are,
Esmeralda.
SKYLER:
Yeah.
Wake up, baby.
Time to party.
Okay. Easy, easy.
Believe it or not,
Esmeralda, right after the party,
your name was changed to Holly.
And l believe, Hank, that
that was around the time.
that we took Aunt Marie
to the insane asylum.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
l dropped her off at the curb.
Then l married Shania Twain
and lived happily ever after.
MARlE:
Ha, ha, ha.
There's Daddy. Speak, Daddy.
Say hello to your daughter.
Oh, uh...
Holly, l am very proud of you.
And l... l think about you
all the time.
ALL:
Aww.
Wherever you go,
whatever you do in life,
always know that you have a family
who loves you very, very much.
Cheers.
ALL: Cheers.
SKYLER:
Oh, my God, it's so cute.
Oh, Carmen. lt's--
Oh, look. Look at that.
lt's adorable.
l love it, Carmen. Thank you.
You're so welcome, honey.
SKYLER:
Thank you.
Look at the little feet.
Okay. Oh.
From me. And Hank.
Oh. What nice
wrapping paper.
Marie always finds
the best wrapping paper.
l do.
Okay.
Let's see. And...
Exciting.
Oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy.
lt's-- lt's a--
A tiara.
Yes.
Oh, wow! Oh.
Marie, is this--?
White gold and several
carats worth of zircons.
Oh, Marie.
You spent too much on this.
You shouldn't have.
You really, really shouldn't.
But it's so--
lt's really-- lt's. . .
lt's sparkly.
Sparkly.
l know.
SKYLER:
Thank you.
Hey, listen, Walt.
You got anything
stronger than beer?
SKYLER: lt's-- lt's great. l love it.
Yeah.
Thank you. Thank you,
sweetie, thank you.
HANK:
Sorry, man. lt's just, you know, after
200 presents, it just gets kind of old.
[WALT LAUGHS]
lt's nice stuff.
lt is, isn't it?
l got just the thing
to go with that.
l'm sorry, man, l wasn't thinking.
No, no, no. lt's okay.
You mind if l have one?
You think that's a good idea?
Hank, l've already got lung cancer.
Okay.
You got me there.
Thanks.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Cuban.
Mm.
l did a little favor for an FBl guy.
Now, l was under
the impression, ahem,
that these were illegal.
Yeah, well, sometimes
forbidden fruit tastes
the sweetest, doesn't it?
lt's funny, isn't it?
How we draw that line.
Yeah.
What line is that?
Well, what's legal, what's illegal.
You know, Cuban cigars, alcohol.
You know, if we were drinking this
in 1 930, we'd be breaking the law.
Another year, we'd be okay.
Mm. Who knows what
will be legal next year.
You mean like pot?
Yeah. Like pot.
Or whatever.
Cocaine? Heroin?
l'm just saying it's arbitrary.
Well, you ought to visit lockup.
You hear a lot of guys
talking like that.
"Hey, man, what, you busting me
with these 1 4 bales of ganja?
lt's all gonna be legal next year
when Willie Nelson's president."
Say it, buddy.
lt don't only go one way either.
l mean, some other stuff
is legal that shouldn't be.
l mean, frigging meth
used to be legal.
Used to sell it over
every counter at every
pharmacy across America.
Thank God they came to
their senses on that one, huh?
Yeah.
Okay.
[GROANS]
Nice party.
Mmm.
A tiara.
A white-gold tiara
for a newborn baby.
Yeah. You know, l think
she got that at Gertrude
Zachary's in Knob Hill.
l mean, that thing must've cost,
like, what, 5 or 600 dollars.
You know, l think
l'm gonna return it.
Are you sure?
She's bound to find out.
Well, maybe l can explain to her
that we need a Diaper Genie
more than a white-gold
baby tiara.
Hey. You know,
l've been thinking
about what you said
to Dr. Delcavoli about
alternative medicine.
No. Don't worry. l'm not
gonna mention that anymore.
No, no, no. What l mean
is that maybe there is
something to it.
Look. They do this
Navajo sweat lodge
up by Farmington.
Healing ceremony.
lt's supposed to be
good for your lungs.
l'm not saying that
l believe in it, but, uh...
Well, it might be an experience.
Really?
You?
ln a sweat lodge.
Ah, l was thinking about driving up
on Friday, coming back Sunday.
l mean, if you're okay with it.
Well, of course l'm okay with that.
Okay.
Sweat lodge?
Yeah.
l'm already sweating.
Help me out.
Okay. Ow.
Hey.
Seventy millimeter tube furnace.
Excellent. This is excellent.
Very good work.
Damn straight.
Okay, hydrogen.
Electrolytically
produced, yes?
Yeah, like you asked.
l mean, this--
This crap wasn't easy to get.
And it's expensive.
Methylamine.
Where's the methylamine?
l don't see the methylamine.
Yeah, well, that's where
l ran into some trouble.
What kind of trouble?
Well, half this crap
l could just buy, right?
But this methylamine. . .
Not so easy. l mean,
they got it locked down tight.
But l did find some pros
who will rip it off for us.
But they want 1 0 grand.
So, what's the problem?
You have the money.
No, had. l spent
almost the whole wad.
l mean, l got
like 2 grand left.
l told you, all this
crap was expensive.
So these thieves,
did they say where they
would be stealing it from?
A chemical supply place,
south of town.
They got guards and security
cameras. They got steel doors.
That's why these dudes
are charging so much.
What?
[♪♪♪]
WALT:
Hmm.
[RATTLlNG]
So why don't we
just steal it ourselves?
Yeah?
How we gonna
do that?
With this.
So, what's this stuff called again?
Thermite.
And that will cut
through a lock?
Because this is supposed
to be one big-ass lock.
ln World War ll,
the Germans had an artillery piece--
lt's the biggest in the world.
--called the Gustav Gun.
And it weighed
a thousand tons.
And the Gustav was capable
of firing a 7-ton shell
and hitting a target,
accurately, 23 miles away.
l mean, you could drop bombs
on it every day for a month
without ever disabling it.
But drop a commando,
one man,
with just a bag of this. . .
and he could melt right through
4 inches of solid steel
and destroy that gun forever.
Jeez.
[COUGHS]
So, yes,
l think it will cut through
any lock we're likely to find.
MAN: You'd like to return this.
SKYLER: lt's very nice, but yes.
Well, it-- lt is from
this store, isn't it?
Oh, yes, it's from this store.
Do you happen to have a receipt?
No, l don't. lt was a gift.
Aha. A gift.
Mm-hm.
Mr. Wilson, could you
step over here, please?
Mr. Wilson, l'd like you to watch
this lady while l phone the police.
Whoa, excuse me?
Ma'am, this item is stolen,
as l'm sure you know.
lt--
Come with me, please.
Oh, yes. l intend
to press charges.
Please do.
We'll be here.
Look, l-- l've never stolen
anything in my life.
All right? l told you,
that tiara was a gift--
A baby-shower gift.
So who gave it to you, then?
l don't think l have
to tell you that.
Ma'am, you don't have
to tell me anything.
You can talk to the police.
And l can tell them how my
daughter-in-law remembers
showing this particular item
to a tall blond woman
who, when her back was turned,
walked right out the door with it.
So there.
Oh, yeah?
Well, then, l can talk
to the Channel Three News.
Yeah, l can tell them how
you people, without a shred--
Without a modicum of evidence,
illegally detained
an innocent pregnant woman
in a dank storeroom.
This is my office.
l feel l'm being held hostage.
Furthermore, l'm not
getting enough air back here.
l don't think-- l don't
think l can breathe.
Oh, my-- Oh, my God. Oh, no.
l'm going into labor.
Yes, l-- Oh!
[BREATHlNG HEAVlLY]
MARlE [ON MESSAGE]:
Hi, you've reached Marie.
Do the beep thing.
Marie, it's Skyler.
l just left Zachary's.
l need to talk to you
immediately.
[PHONE BEEPS]
WALT:
Where is the guard?
He's supposed to be coming by.
Do you think he already passed?
JESSE:
Look, l don't-- l don't know.
Okay. Wait, there he is.
There he is.
WALT:
Yeah, yeah, l see him.
JESSE:
Okay, wait till he passes.
Okay, it's clear.
Here.
What the hell is this?
lt's all they had.
Then you go to another store.
lf this is all they had,
you're in the wrong place.
Just put it on.
Should've-- Of course.
[METAL SNAPPlNG]
Okay, okay.
Okay. This is it.
Oh, God.
JESSE:
Okay.
JESSE: Get--
WALT: What?
JESSE: Look.
GUARD:
Hey, Jimmy, l'm stopping...
WALT:
He's not supposed to
come back. What's he doing?
Oh, my God.
MAN [OVER RADlO]:
Hope everything comes out all right.
He's going to the crapper.
Oh, God.
Okay. You coming, man? Come on.
What are you doing?
Okay, there it is.
ls this gonna be loud?
You'll find out
in about 1 0 seconds.
Stand back.
Jesus.
[ALARM BUZZlNG AND RlNGlNG]
Come on, come on.
[RATTLlNG]
GUARD:
Hey, what's going on?
[♪♪♪]
Where are the gallon jugs?
l don't--
God!
What?
Let's just take this.
Come on, come on.
What the--?
Damn it.
WALT:
What the hell are you
doing opening the door?
JESSE:
How are we
gonna take this thing out?
WALT:
Come on. Take that.
Lift.
[BOTH GRUNTlNG]
JESSE: God.
WALT: Jeez.
Hey. Somebody?
MAN [OVER RADlO]:
Billy, you back from
the crapper yet?
Let me out of here.
l'm gonna kick somebody's ass.
The alarm's going off. Check it out.
Billy? Billy?
Jimmy? Help!
[ENGlNE STALLlNG]
Come on, man, let me try it.
How is it gonna be any different?
Can l just try it?
Fine, fine, go ahead.
Jesus. Okay.
All right.
[ENGlNE STALLlNG]
[ENGlNE STARTS]
Yeah, baby. See?
Eat it. Okay, l'm the king.
Yeah, okay.
l'm the king.
[ENGlNE STOPS]
Oh, no. No, no, no.
That didn't sound good.
Oh, God.
Well, this thing's
not going anywhere.
We're not cooking
in my damn driveway,
l'll tell you that.
WALT:
God.
What part of "slow it down"
did you not understand?
What are you talking--?
l'm-- lt's heavy, man.
lt got away from me.
WALT:
Okay. All right.
Now, that's good, that's good.
Now just bring it up,
bring it up.
Easy, easy, easy. Okay.
Your real-estate agent,
when is she supposed
to come back?
Oh, shit.
Yeah. l don't know.
l'll make damn sure
she doesn't.
Good call, yo.
[CELL PHONE RlNGlNG
AND VlBRATlNG]
WALT:
Keep the temperature
steady at 425 degrees.
We'll need to run it
two more hours
to have enough to make
4.5 pounds.
Four and a half, not 4?
Two pounds pays, two go back.
Four and a half pounds
puts us $44,000 ahead.
Each.
Right on, man.
Right on.
With the amount of methylamine
that we got last night,
we can make
4.5 pounds a week for. ..
Well, for the foreseeable future.
How long is, uh, that gonna be?
l mean, in your, uh, situation.
How much cash
do you need?
[SlGHS]
More.
[PEOPLE CHATTERlNG]
[GASPS]
Someone's in the yard.
Shh.
MAN:
Yeah, this is definitely the one.
WOMAN:
lt's pretty.
Actually, l like it.
We could pull that out
and put in a closet.
Just a little--
We'll have to bring that down.
MAN:
l thought you didn't
like that type of thing.
WOMAN:
Oh, no. No, l don't.
MAN:
Right, right.
Shh. Shh.
Was there, by any chance,
scheduled for this afternoon,
an open house?
l left her a message, man.
lt's not my fault.
l don't care how you do it,
just keep them out of here.
Do you understand?
Yeah.
All right, go.
[KEZlAH JONES'
"BEAUTlFUL EMlLE"
PLAYlNG OVER SPEAKERS]
[WOMEN CHATTERlNG]
WOMAN:
Absolutely.
You know, you can't
duck me forever.
What?
Come on, l left you
like 1 5 messages.
When l went to your
office, you snuck
out the back way.
l didn't sneak.
l was going to lunch.
Jeez, Skyler, what are you,
the paranoid police?
You know what, Marie?
Marie, l have never been
so humiliated in my life.
That-- Ahem.
[WHlSPERS]
That tiara.
They accused me,
at Zachary's, of shoplifting it.
[WHlSPERlNG]
What were you doing at Zachary's?
[SlGHS]
l was returning it.
[lN NORMAL VOlCE]
You were returning it.
Why would you return it?
[lN NORMAL VOlCE]
lt just wasn't--
Marie, what is wrong with you?
Can you please tell me that?
Can you tell me why
you'd do such a thing?
What does that mean?
Does that mean you don't know?
That...means that l have
no idea what the hell
you're even talking about.
You have no idea
what l'm talking about.
The shop--
[WHlSPERlNG]
The shoplifting. No idea?
[lN NORMAL VOlCE]
You're not going to
admit this, are you?
[SCOFFS]
l can't really admit
to something
when l have no knowledge
of what it is that l'm admitting.
MAN:
Would you like
that gift-wrapped?
WOMAN:
Yes, actually.
Don't forget
to sign in.
[SNlFFlNG]
Thank you.
MAN:
You're right.
Look at this wall here.
Yo!
[KNOCKlNG ON DOOR]
MAN: Excuse me,
l'd just like to see
the basement.
Yeah, well, it's occupied.
lt's not a bathroom.
Hey!
l just want to see the basement.
What's the big deal?
You ain't seeing
the basement, bitch.
You got that? ls that
sinking in? Now, beat it.
All you all,
house is not for sale.
Get the hell out!
[SlGHS]
Ahh.
Hey.
So how was it?
Was it an experience?
Yeah.
lt was definitely
an experience.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
[SNlFFlNG]
What's that smell?
Oh, yeah, it's.. .
sacred Navajo herbs.
You know.
[GROANS]
[SlGHS]
Hey, everything okay?
No.
Not really.
[CHUCKLES]
Actually, not at all.
[SlGHS]
You know that tiara
that Marie gave us?
Yeah.
Well, she stole it. Yep.
l practically got arrested
trying to return it at the store.
Oh, my God.
l mean, she refuses to admit it.
She refuses to apologize.
l don't know what to do.
Hm.
People sometimes
do things for their families.
do things for their families?
And, what,
that justifies stealing?
Well.. .
Wow. That must've been
some sweat lodge.
Are you even listening
to the words coming
out of your mouth?
What would you do
if it were me?
What do you mean,
if it were you?
lf it were me, what would you do?
Would you divorce me?
Would you turn me in to the police?
You don't want to find out.
You want
something to eat?
Um, no, thanks.
What is this shit?
This is blue.
We used a different
chemical process,
but it is every bit as pure.
lt may be blue,
but it's the bomb.
[SNlFFS]
Ah! Tight, tight, tight, yeah.
Blue, yellow, pink.
Whatever, man. Just keep
bringing me that.
Ahh.
4.6.
Come on.
And what'd l say, man?
This guy can cook.
You're all right, man.
You're all right.
We're gonna make
a lot of money together.
Just remember
who you're working for.
What did you say?
l'm just saying, they gotta know
that they're working for you.
TUCO:
Like they don't
already know that?
Are you saying
that they're stupid?
No, l'm just--
l'm just saying.
Okay, so you're not saying
that they're stupid.
So l don't understand.
Are you saying that l'm stupid?
MAN:
No, come on, Tuco.
l'm just-- l'm just saying.
No, you're just
speaking for me!
Like l ain't got the goddamn
sense to speak for myself!
ls that it? ls that
what you're doing?
Tuco.
Hey, why don't we
all just relax, huh?
[LAUGHlNG]
Heisenberg says "relax."
[SPEAKS lN SPANlSH]
l'm relaxed. l'm relaxed.
l'm relax--
[TUCO GRUNTlNG]
Whoo! Damn, man!
Look at that! Look!
Whew!
That is messed up.
Okay, Heisenberg. Next week.
[LAUGHS]
[GNARLS BARKLEY'S
"WHO'S GONNA
SAVE MY SOUL" PLAYlNG]
[ENGlNE STARTS]
[TRUCK DRlVES OFF]